http://www.cabinetmagazine.org/information/privacy.php

MagazineKioskBooksActivitiesShopSubscribe
Welcome to cabinetmagazine.org. Cabinet magazine provides the services on this website to you subject to the following conditions. If you visit, shop, or subscribe at cabinetmagazine.org, you accept these conditions. Please read them carefully.
Privacy Please review our Privacy Notice to understand the policies of cabinetmagazine.org.
Electronic Communication
When you visit cabinetmagazine.org or send emails to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you via email or by posting notices on this site. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures, and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communication be in writing.
Copyright
All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, images, audio clips, downloads, and software, is the property of Cabinet magazine or is published by Cabinet magazine with the permission of the copyright holders, and all content on this site is protected by United States and international copyright laws. The compilation of all content on this site is the exclusive property of Cabinet magazine and is protected by United States and international copyright laws.
Trademarks
Cabinet magazine, Immaterial Inc., and any other Cabinet magazine graphics, logos, page headers, icons and scripts are trademarks or trade dress of Cabinet magazine. Cabinet magazine's trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not Cabinet magazine's or in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers. You may use them in a manner that disparages or discredits Cabinet magazine, so long as no other provision of these Conditions of Use is violated. All other trademarks not owned by Cabinet magazine that appear on this site are the property of their respective owners, who may or may not be affiliated with or connected to Cabinet magazine.
License and Site Access
Cabinet magazine grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of this site and not to modify or republish it, or any portion of it, except with the express written consent of Cabinet magazine. This site, or any portion of it, or any derivative uses of it, may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without the express written consent of Cabinet magazine. Any unauthorized use of this site terminates the permission or license granted by Cabinet magazine. You are granted a limited, revocable, non-exclusive right to create a hyperlink to the homepage of cabinetmagazine.org. You may not use any Cabinet magazine logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without express written permission.
Your Account
If you use this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password, if required for a given transaction, and you are responsible for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password, or that originate with your computer. If you are under 18, you may use Cabinet magazine only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. Cabinet magazine reserves the right to refuse service, terminate accounts, remove or edit content, or cancel an order in its sole discretion.
Viewer- and Reader-Submitted Content
Viewers of the site may submit material to cabinetmagazine.org, via such means as Cabinet magazine may choose, at its discretion, to make available, so long as such material is not illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, or otherwise injurious to third parties or objectionable and does consist of or contain software viruses, worms, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of spam. You may not use a false email address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of submitted material. Cabinet magazine reserves the right (but not the obligation) to remove or edit such content.
If you do post or submit material, and unless we indicate otherwise, you grant Cabinet magazine a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media. You grant Cabinet magazine the right to use the name that you submit in connection with such content, if it chooses. You represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the content that you post; that the content is accurate; that the use of the content you supply does not violate this policy and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify Cabinet magazine for all claims resulting from content you supply. Cabinet magazine has the right but not the obligation to monitor and edit or remove any activity or content. Cabinet magazine takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any content posted by you or any third party.
Risk of Loss
All items purchased from Cabinet magazine are made pursuant to a shipment contract. This means that the risk of loss and title for such items passes to you upon our delivery to the carrier.
Product Descriptions
Cabinet magazine attempts to be as accurate as possible. However, Cabinet magazine does not warrant that product descriptions or other content on this site is accurate, complete, reliable, current, or error-free. If a product offered by Cabinet magazine itself is not as described, your sole remedy is to return it in unused condition.
Sites Linked To From Cabinetmagazine.org
Cabinet magazine is not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of or content posted upon, any website which we may link to from cabinetmagazine.org. Cabinet magazine does not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, product, and content or all these and any other third parties. You should carefully review their privacy statements and other conditions of use.
Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liability
This site is provided by Cabinet magazine on an "as is" and "as available" basis. Cabinet magazine makes no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of this site or the information, content, materials, or products included on this site. You expressly agree that your use of this site is at your sole risk.
To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Cabinet magazine disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. Cabinet magazine does not warrant that this site, its servers, or email sent from cabinetmagazine.org are free of viruses or other harmful components. Cabinet magazine will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use of this site, including, but not limited to, direct, indirect, incidental, punitive, and consequential damages.
Certain state laws do not allow limitations on implied warranties or the exclusion or limitation of certain damages. If these laws apply to you, some or all of the above disclaimers, exclusions, or limitations may not apply to you, and you might have additional rights.
Applicable Law
By visiting cabinetmagazine.org, you agree that the laws of the state of New York, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Conditions of Use and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Cabinet magazine.
Disputes
Any dispute relating in any way to your visit to cabinetmagazine.org or to products you purchase through cabinetmagazine.org shall to submitted to arbitration in New York City, New York, except that, to the extent you have in any manner violated or threatened to violate Cabinet magazine's intellectual property rights, Cabinet magazine may seek injunctive or other appropriate relief in any state or federal court in the state of New York, and you consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in such courts. Arbitration under this agreement shall be conducted under the rules pertaining to a single arbitrator then prevailing of the American Arbitration Association. The arbitrator's award shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction.
Site Policies, Modification, and Severability
Please review any other policies posted on this site, such as our privacy policy and our returns policy, which also govern your visit to Cabinet magazine. We reserve the right to make changes to our site, policies, and these Conditions of Use at any time. If any of these conditions shall be deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that condition shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining condition.
Privacy Statement
Cabinet magazine knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting cabinetmagazine.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
Sharing Information
Any information you submit to us will be used only to fulfill the request you have made. Under no circumstances will we barter, sell, or trade your information with any other institutions, organizations, or companies.
Cookies
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as a shopping cart.
Security
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
We reveal none of the digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number securely to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
